[{"answer": "Well, like I said today, Piers, is that I wanted to be able to put a face and a voice to those women out there that didn't want to or could not, for whatever their reasons are -- I wanted to speak about this because it was -- I wanted to tell the truth.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "What made you do that?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I first met Herman in 1994 -- 1997 when I was employed at the Educational Foundation of the National Restaurant Association.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "When did you first meet Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Yes, I was terminated.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "And then you were laid off, is that right?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "And you then made contact with Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "That was Herman's.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "And whose idea was it to have dinner?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I had a glass of wine, yes.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "And did you drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "And did Mr. Cain drink?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I -- you know, I really can't remember.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "I mean, how much did you have together?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Was he a gentleman during dinner?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "He -- not so much during dinner, but he said that he would look into it.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Did he say then that he would be able to help you perhaps get your job back?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Well, it was his because I had to get a ride back to the hotel because I didn't have the car.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "And whose idea was it to then get in the car together?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Very, very much so because, first of all, he had met my boyfriend.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Were you shocked by what happened?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Are you concerned about the impact of all this on your child?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Have you at any stage in the last 14 years made any approach to Herman Cain to get some kind of apology from him?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, when you tell someone, you know, this is not why I'm here, please drive me back, and I was very stern and, yes, he knew -- I wouldn't say he was apologetic, but he knew I wasn't happy about what went on.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Was he aware that he had gone too far, if what you say is true?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I only told two people.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "How many other people have known about what happened?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "We're not going to name them, Piers, but we are identifying them as we did today as a physician that she was dating who has provided a declaration under penalty of perjury to us, which we have signed.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "And who are they?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Well, they didn't describe me the way most people would describe me, which is a women's rights attorney, which I have been for 36 years and we've done more sexual harassment cases in our law firm, in our private law firm, than any other law firm in the country, and won literally hundreds of millions of dollars for victims of sexual harassment.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "How do you counter that charge?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I believe -- up until this point, I believe that he first needs to apologize and he needs to admit it.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Sharon, let me ask you, did you believe that Herman Cain should now stand down as a candidate for the Republican Party nomination?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "He tried to ask me more details, and I said I really don't want to talk about it.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Sharon, let me ask you, how did your boyfriend react when you told him at the time what had happened?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "To be honest with you, right now I haven't even watched any of the media.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "How is this affecting you emotionally?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Are you considering filing charges against him?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I believe the statute of limitations would have run out by now.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I don't think we can have anyone in the White House who is unable to tell the truth.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "My final question to you, Sharon, is simply, do you think that Herman Cain should become president of the United States?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Not surprised, Piers, especially when you take into consideration the amount of time that the jury deliberated.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Were you surprised by the verdict in the end?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Yes, it was from right behind me.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Was that from members of his family?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "OWLANDS: Well, his medical license in each of the states where he practices will have to be dealt with by those medical board.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "What are you anticipating will be the outcome here?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think what went wrong was a lot of the pretrial rulings that were made by the court in reference to some of the evidence that we planned to offer for the jury to consider.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What went wrong?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Well, he was clearly devastated.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "And how did Dr. Murray react after he realized that he had been found guilty of effectively killing Michael Jackson, one of the most iconic entertainers of our lifetime?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Dr. Murray is currently at the Inmate Reception Center where he's being -- going through the booking process.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Where is Dr. Murray tonight?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "What do you think would be a fair punishment given that he's been convicted?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, we have to remember what happened here on June 25th of 2009, Dr. Murray did not have Mr. Jackson on a drip.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "I mean, you would have been uneasy as a lawyer about that situation, that state of affairs, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Excuse me, would we be appealing?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I'm not concerned about his mental condition.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Are you concerned about his mental condition?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well, the verdict was certainly reasonable verdict.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Right verdict, do you think?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "It did seem extraordinary.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "And why wasn't he ready to argue that bail motion more effectively?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Looking back, do you have any regrets now about the way the jury composition was made up?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, I hope the lawyers do a better job on sentencing than they did on bail.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Would you think that would be an appropriate sentence given that he's been convicted?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "It was a great interview, by the way.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Do you think she has credibility?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "In the words, piers, of a famous actor, I'm mad as hell, and I ain't going to take it any more.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "How do you feel now that this doctor that you had so much time for and support for has been convicted of the death of Michael Jackson?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Conrad Murray was the only man on this planet that loved Michael Jackson enough to try to help him.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Do you think that Conrad Murray has been stitched up here?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "You're clearly feeling very emotional about Dennis.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Where the hell were they when he was shooting himself with Demerol?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Just when I testified.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "Have you had the chance to talk to Conrad Murray?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "I mean, if you had the chance now, what would you say to him?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I was happy.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "How did you feel when you saw that Conrad Murray had been convicted?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Well, one, when I read -- did my testimony and my report, I just reviewed Dr. Murray's very own words to investigation.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "From your belief, from what you read and heard, what do you think?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "No, I think hopefully it is over.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Or will it still carry on but just in a discreet way?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, I was happy in some regards, Piers.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What was your reaction to the verdict today?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Absolutely not, I don't.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "I also want to ask you, as I would ask anyone I guess involved in this, do you have any sympathy with Conrad Murray, who has always said he was just trying to help Michael?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "No sympathy.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "So no sympathy from you towards Conrad Murray?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "You tell me.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Let me ask you, Lavelle, how could that be possible?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I was shocked to hear it.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Michael Prince, when you heard the now infamous tape of Michael slurring and sounding completely out of it, were you as shocked as everybody else, given that you were working so closely with him?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, Michael's legacy, unequivocally, Piers, is going to be his children.", "docId": "111107pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "What do you think Michael's legacy should be?", "qSentId": 522}]